[Music]
[âm nhạc]
[Applause] We
[Vỗ tay]
respectfully bow to the Buddha, whose boundless compassion
kính lạy Đức Thế Tôn lòng từ bi Vô Lượng
accepts the offerings of the forest and the
Thọ nhận món Lâm trọc
blacksmith. We
đổ thợ sắt cùn
respectfully bow to the Buddha, whose compassion
định lạy Đức Thế Tôn lòng từ bi của ngài
is like the sun shining, dispelling all dangers,
là mặt trời soi chiếu xóa tàn các hiểm
for he is the sun shining, dispelling all sorrows. The compassionate Buddha, the virtuous one, whose body is free from serious
vì người là mặt trời soi chiếu xóa tan
illness,
Hiền Nghi bậc thánh thân không bệnh
thinks of the body as not being sick. The Buddha, the enlightened one, whose compassion is
hiểm nghĩ thân bệnh không Đạt Đạo Thế
like the Buddha, the
Tôn lòng từ bi Tao hỏi thế tôn bậc đạo
teacher who saves the world. The Buddha, whose compassion is like the
sư độ đời Thế Tôn lòng từ bi của ngài
sun shining, dispelling all beliefs. He is the sun shining, dispelling all sorrows.
an lành Thanh Tâm
[Music]
[âm nhạc]
[Applause] We
[Vỗ tay]
respectfully bow to the Buddha, whose boundless compassion
kính lạy Đức Thế Tôn lòng từ bi Vô Lượng
accepts the offerings of the forest and the blacksmith, cultivating
Thọ nhận món Lâm trọc đổ thợ sắt vun đắp
love again. The Buddha, whose compassionate love is like the
tình lại Đức Thế Tôn lòng từ bi thương
sun shining, dispelling all
ngày là mặt trời soi chiếu xóa tan các
beliefs. He is the sun shining, dispelling all sorrows.
niềm tin người là mặt trời soi chiếu Xóa
[Music]
[âm nhạc]
rarely does the Buddha, whose body is free from serious
hiếm khi bậc thánh thân không bệnh
illness, thinks of the body as not being sick. The Buddha, whose
hiểm nghĩ thân bệnh không Đạt Đạo Thế
compassion is sublime, the Buddha meets the
Tôn lòng từ bi cao vời thế tôn gặp đạo
teacher of the world. The Buddha,
sư đời
whose compassion gives us
Thế Tôn lòng từ bi của ngài cho chúng
eternal peace. The Buddha, whose
con mãi mãi an lành Thanh Tâm
compassion is sublime, the
Thế Tôn lòng từ bi cao vời thế tôn bậc
Buddha, the teacher of the world. The Buddha, whose compassion
đạo sư đồ gửi thế tôn lòng từ bi của
gives us eternal peace.  forever
ngài cho chúng con mãi mãi
[music]
[âm nhạc]
[Applause]
[Vỗ tay]